var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "أَحَدٌ",
        "answer": "anyone",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "aḥadun",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدٌ",
        "answer": "anyone",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "aḥadun",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "387",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "388",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "389",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "390",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضُ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "457",
        "tlit": "l-arḍu",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِرَمَ",
        "answer": "Iram",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "irama",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَأْكُلُونَ",
        "answer": "And you consume",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "watakulūna",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْلًا",
        "answer": "devouring",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "aklan",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "Which",
        "pcklId": "1417",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "1418",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Who",
        "pcklId": "1419",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "739",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "And as for",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "fa-ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "But",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "wa-ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانُ",
        "answer": "man",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "l-insānu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانُ",
        "answer": "man",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "l-insānu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنَّىٰ",
        "answer": "but how",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "wa-annā",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبِلَادِ",
        "answer": "the cities",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-bilādi",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبِلَادِ",
        "answer": "the lands",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-bilādi",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْتَلَاهُ",
        "answer": "try him",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "ib'talāhu",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْتَلَاهُ",
        "answer": "He try him",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "ib'talāhu",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمًّا",
        "answer": "immense",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "jamman",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّتِي",
        "answer": "My Paradise",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "jannatī",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَابُوا",
        "answer": "carved out",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "jābū",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَاءَ",
        "answer": "And comes",
        "pcklId": "274",
        "tlit": "wajāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجِيءَ",
        "answer": "And is brought",
        "pcklId": "275",
        "tlit": "wajīa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتُحِبُّونَ",
        "answer": "And you love",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "watuḥibbūna",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُبًّا",
        "answer": "(with) love",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "ḥubban",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِجْرٍ",
        "answer": "who understand",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ḥij'rin",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحَاضُّونَ",
        "answer": "you feel the urge",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "taḥāḍḍūna",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِحَيَاتِي",
        "answer": "for my life",
        "pcklId": "171",
        "tlit": "liḥayātī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُخْلَقْ",
        "answer": "had been created",
        "pcklId": "177",
        "tlit": "yukh'laq",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَادْخُلِي",
        "answer": "So enter",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "fa-ud'khulī",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَادْخُلِي",
        "answer": "And enter",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "wa-ud'khulī",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُكَّتِ",
        "answer": "is leveled",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "dukkati",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَكًّا",
        "answer": "pounded",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "dakkan",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَكًّا",
        "answer": "(and) crushed",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "dakkan",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَذَكَّرُ",
        "answer": "will remember",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "yatadhakkaru",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الذِّكْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "the remembrance",
        "pcklId": "195",
        "tlit": "l-dhik'rā",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَ",
        "answer": "you see",
        "pcklId": "257",
        "tlit": "tara",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "946",
        "tlit": "rabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "947",
        "tlit": "rabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "948",
        "tlit": "rabbaka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّهُ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "949",
        "tlit": "rabbuhu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "My Lord",
        "pcklId": "950",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "My Lord",
        "pcklId": "951",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "952",
        "tlit": "rabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكِ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "953",
        "tlit": "rabbiki",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "ارْجِعِي",
        "answer": "Return",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "ir'jiʿī",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِزْقَهُ",
        "answer": "his provision",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "riz'qahu",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَبِالْمِرْصَادِ",
        "answer": "(is) surely Ever Watchful",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "labil-mir'ṣādi",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَاضِيَةً",
        "answer": "well pleased",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "rāḍiyatan",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرْضِيَّةً",
        "answer": "and pleasing",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "marḍiyyatan",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْرِ",
        "answer": "it passes",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yasri",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمِسْكِينِ",
        "answer": "the poor",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "l-mis'kīni",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَوْطَ",
        "answer": "scourge",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "sawṭa",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالشَّفْعِ",
        "answer": "And the even",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wal-shafʿi",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَصَبَّ",
        "answer": "So poured",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "faṣabba",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّخْرَ",
        "answer": "the rocks",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-ṣakhra",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَفًّا",
        "answer": "rank",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ṣaffan",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَفًّا",
        "answer": "(upon) rank",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ṣaffan",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَعَامِ",
        "answer": "feed",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "ṭaʿāmi",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَغَوْا",
        "answer": "transgressed",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ṭaghaw",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُطْمَئِنَّةُ",
        "answer": "who is satisfied",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-muṭ'ma-inatu",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادِي",
        "answer": "My slaves",
        "pcklId": "262",
        "tlit": "ʿibādī",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعَذِّبُ",
        "answer": "will punish",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "yuʿadhibu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٍ",
        "answer": "(of) punishment",
        "pcklId": "361",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābin",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابَهُ",
        "answer": "(as) His punishment",
        "pcklId": "362",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābahu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَشْرٍ",
        "answer": "ten",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ʿashrin",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِمَادِ",
        "answer": "lofty pillars",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-ʿimādi",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعَادٍ",
        "answer": "with Aad",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "biʿādin",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْفَجْرِ",
        "answer": "By the dawn",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wal-fajri",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَسَادَ",
        "answer": "corruption",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "l-fasāda",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَلَ",
        "answer": "dealt",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "faʿala",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَدَرَ",
        "answer": "and restricts",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "faqadara",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدَّمْتُ",
        "answer": "I had sent forth",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "qaddamtu",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَسَمٌ",
        "answer": "(not) an oath",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "qasamun",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَقُولُ",
        "answer": "he says",
        "pcklId": "1608",
        "tlit": "fayaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَقُولُ",
        "answer": "then he says",
        "pcklId": "1609",
        "tlit": "fayaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُ",
        "answer": "He will say",
        "pcklId": "1610",
        "tlit": "yaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَكْثَرُوا",
        "answer": "And (made) much",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "fa-aktharū",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَكْرَمَهُ",
        "answer": "and is generous to him",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "fa-akramahu",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْرَمَنِ",
        "answer": "has honored me",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "akramani",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُكْرِمُونَ",
        "answer": "you honor",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "tuk'rimūna",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمًّا",
        "answer": "altogether",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "lamman",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَيَالٍ",
        "answer": "And the nights",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "walayālin",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّيْلِ",
        "answer": "And the night",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "wa-al-layli",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلُهَا",
        "answer": "like them",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "mith'luhā",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَلَكُ",
        "answer": "and the Angels",
        "pcklId": "195",
        "tlit": "wal-malaku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَالَ",
        "answer": "wealth",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "l-māla",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَعَّمَهُ",
        "answer": "and favors him",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wanaʿʿamahu",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّفْسُ",
        "answer": "soul",
        "pcklId": "295",
        "tlit": "l-nafsu",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهَانَنِ",
        "answer": "(has) humiliated me",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ahānani",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَوْتَادِ",
        "answer": "stakes",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-awtādi",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْوَتْرِ",
        "answer": "and the odd",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wal-watri",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوثِقُ",
        "answer": "will bind",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yūthiqu",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَثَاقَهُ",
        "answer": "(as) His binding",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "wathāqahu",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْوَادِ",
        "answer": "in the valley",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "bil-wādi",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "التُّرَاثَ",
        "answer": "the inheritance",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "l-turātha",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَتِيمَ",
        "answer": "the orphan",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "l-yatīma",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "89",
        "ayah": "17"
    }
]; 
export default words;